Let's use the "querySelectorAll" method to select all of the "h2" elements on the page.
لنستخدم أسلوب "querySelectorAll" لتحديد جميع عناصر "h2" في الصفحة.
So running a "document.querySelectAll" and then passing an
حسنًا، إن تشغيل "document.querySelectAll" ثم تمرير
"h2" will return a list of all of "h2" elements on the page.
"h2" سيرجع قائمة بجميع عناصر "h2" على الصفحة.
Now it's important to remember that this is not an array.
الآن من المهم أن تتذكروا أنها ليست مصفوفة.
This is actually a special list called a "NodeList."
إنها قائمة خاصة تسمى "NodeList."
Because it's not actually an array,
نظرًا لعدم كونها مصفوفة حقًا،
we can't use the array method ".map" to loop over the items in the array.
لا يمكننا استخدام أسلوب المصفوفات ".map" لإنشاء تكرار حلقي فوق العناصر في المصفوفة.
However, NodeList, let's look at it,
ومع ذلك، فإن NodeList، لنلقِ نظرة عليه،
does provide a, where is it here?
يوفر، أين يوجد ذلك هنا؟
"forEach" method and this "forEach" is very similar to the "forEach" of the array method.
أسلوب "forEach" الذي يشبه "forEach" الموجود في أسلوب المصفوفة جدًا.
However, if we scroll down to the bottom here,
ومع ذلك، إذا مرَّرنا إلى الأسفل هنا،
the browser support for the "forEach" method is not fully supported by every browser.
سنجد أن دعم المتصفح للأسلوب "forEach" غير مدعوم بشكل كامل من كل متصفح.
But that's all right. If we wanted to loop over our items in this list,
لكن هذا جيد. إذا أردنا إنشاء تكرار حلقي لعناصرنا في هذا القائمة،
we can just use a "for loop."
يمكننا استخدام "التكرارات الحلقية for."
First, let's store all of the returned elements in a variable.
لنقم أولًا بتخزين جميع العناصر الراجعة في متغير.
You don't want to watch me write a "for loop," so let me just paste it in some code.
نظرًا لأنكم لا ترغبون في مشاهدتي أكتب "التكرارات الحلقية for"، لذا دعوني أنسخها في جزء من الكود.
So this will loop over every item in the "listOfElements" list.
حسنًا، إن ذلك سيجري تكرارًا حلقيًا لكل عنصر في قائمة "listOfElements".
If we scroll back up here towards the top,
إذا مررنا للأعلى مرة أخرى إلى الجزء العلوي،
we can see that the first item in the list is this heading right here.
يمكننا أن نرى أن العنصر الأول في القائمة هو هذا العنوان الموجود هنا.